A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia 1976-2003
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Seldom Used Permanent Files (Box 35-47)
  - Development - University of Virginia Project on Women and Philanthropy 2000 (Box-folder 42:7)
  - Medical Center - Autonomy 1996 Jan.-Jun. (Box-folder 42:8)
  - Medical Center - Autonomy 1995 Nov.-Dec. (Box-folder 43:1)
  - Medical Center - Autonomy 1993 Dec.-1995 Oct. (Box-folder 43:2)
  - Medical Center - Blue Ridge Hospital 1981-1994 (Box-folder 43:3)
  - Medical Center - Children's Rehabilitation Center 1987-1999 (Box-folder 43:4)
  - Medical Center - Hospital Advisory Board 1990-1994 (Box-folder 43:5)
  - Medical Center - Integration Committee 2001 (Box-folder 43:6)
  - Medical Center - Permanent 1998 Aug.-1999 Dec. (Box-folder 43:7)
  - Medical Center - Permanent 1997 Apr.-Dec. (Box-folder 43:8)
  - Medical Center - Permanent 1995 Jan.-1997 (Box-folder 44:1)
  - Medical Center - Permanent 1994 Jan.-Nov. (Box-folder 44:2)
  - Medical Center - Permanent 1993 Nov.-Dec. (Box-folder 44:3)
  - Medical Center - Policy, Promotions, & Tenure 1976 (Box-folder 44:4)
  - Medical Center - QualChoice 1997-1998 (Box-folder 44:5)
  - Medical Center - Virginia Health Policy Center 1998 (Box-folder 44:6)
  - Medical Center - Virginia Neurological Institute 1996 Jun.-1997 Aug. (Box-folder 44:7)
  - Medical Center - Virginia Neurological Institute 1993 Dec.-1995 Dec. (Box-folder 44:8)
  - Medical Center - Virginia Neurological Institute 1993 Jul.-Nov. (Box-folder 45:1)
  - Miller Center 2002 Mar.-Jun. (Box-folder 45:2)
  - Miller Center 2002 Jan.-Feb. (Box-folder 45:3)
  - Miller Center 2001 Oct.-Dec. (Box-folder 45:4)
  - Miller Center 2001 Aug.-Sep. (Box-folder 45:5)
  - Miller Center 2001 Apr.-Jul. (Box-folder 45:6)
  - Miller Center 2001 Jan.-Mar. (Box-folder 45:7)
  - Miller Center 2000 Jan.-Dec. (Box-folder 46:1)
  - Miller Center 1997 Oct.-1999 Oct. (Box-folder 46:2)
  - Miller Center 1996 Nov.-1997 Sep. (Box-folder 46:3)
  - Physics - Southeastern Universities Research Association 1995 Feb.-1997 Nov. (Box-folder 46:4)
  - Physics - Southeastern Universities Research Association 1993 Aug.-1994 Dec. (Box-folder 46:5)
  - Physics - Southeastern Universities Research Association 1992 Jan.-1993 Jul. (Box-folder 46:6)
  - Physics - Southeastern Universities Research Association 1990 Jan.-1991 Dec. (Box-folder 46:7)
  - Physics - Southeastern Universities Research Association 1988 Sep.-1989 Oct. (Box-folder 47:1)
  - Physics - Southeastern Universities Research Association - Bylaws 1980 Sep.-1985 Jul. (Box-folder 47:2)
  - Physics - Southeastern Universities Research Association - Bylaws 1980 Jul. (Box-folder 47:3)
  - Physics - Southeastern Universities Research Association - Council of Presidents & Board of Trustees Lists 1980-1984 (Box-folder 47:4)
  - Physics - Southeastern Universities Research Association - Minutes 1981-1986 (Box-folder 47:5)
  - South Africa - General 2000-2001 (Box-folder 47:6)
- Series III: Committee Files (Box 47)
  - University Committees - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 47:7)
  - Athletics Advisory Council 2001-2003 (Box-folder 47:8)
  - Benefits Committee 2001-2003 (Box-folder 47:9)
  - Commencement & Convocations Committee - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 47:10)
  - Commencement & Convocations Committee - Subcommittee on Processions 2001-2002 (Box-folder 47:11)
  - Commencement & Convocations Committee - Subcommittee on Public Occasions 2001-2002 (Box-folder 47:12)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Committee 2001-2003 (Box-folder 47:13)
  - Financial Aid Committee 2001-2003 (Box-folder 47:14)
  - Information Technology Committee 2001-2003 (Box-folder 47:15)
  - Libraries Committee 2001-2003 (Box-folder 47:16)
  - Master Planning Council 2001 (Box-folder 47:17)
  - Names Committee 2001-2002 (Box-folder 47:18)
  - Public Art 2001-2003 (Box-folder 47:19)
  - Radiation Safety Committee 2001-2002 (Box-folder 47:20)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award Committee 2001-2003 (Box-folder 47:21)
  - Undergraduate Admissions Committee 2001-2003 (Box-folder 47:22)
  - University Press of Virginia Advisory Board 2001-2003 (Box-folder 47:23)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review Board 2001-2002 (Box-folder 47:24)
  - Virginia Status of University Students Committee 2001-2003 (Box-folder 47:25)
  - Women's Leadership Council 2000-2003 (Box-folder 47:26)
- Series IV: Restricted Files (Box 48-54)
  - "A-F" Miscellaneous (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 48:1)
  - "G-W" Miscellaneous (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 48:2)
  - "B-W" Miscellaneous (pulled from Seldom Used Files) 1983-2002 (Box-folder 48:3)
  - Admissions - General (pulled from General Files 2002 May-Jun. (Box-folder 48:4)
  - Admissions - General (pulled from General Files 2002 Mar.-Apr. (Box-folder 48:5)
  - Admissions - General (pulled from General Files 2002 Jan.-Feb. (Box-folder 48:6)
  - Admissions - General (pulled from General Files 2001 Nov.-Dec. (Box-folder 48:7)
  - Admissions - General (pulled from General Files 2001 Aug.-Oct. (Box-folder 49:1)
  - Admissions - Law (pulled from General Files 2001-2002 (Box-folder 49:2)
  - Admissions - Medical (pulled from General Files 2001-2002 (Box-folder 49:3)
  - Applications for Positions "A-G" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 49:4)
  - Applications for Positions "H-W" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 49:5)
  - Financial Aid to Students Office (pulled from General Files) 2001 (Box-folder 49:6)
  - Gifts & Grants "A" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 49:7)
  - Gifts & Grants "Ba-Bi" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 49:8)
  - Gifts & Grants "Bl-By" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 50:1)
  - Gifts & Grants "Ca-Cl" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 50:2)
  - Gifts & Grants "Co-Cr" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 50:3)
  - Gifts & Grants "Da-De" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 50:4)
  - Gifts & Grants "Di-Du" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 50:5)
  - Gifts & Grants "E" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 50:6)
  - Gifts & Grants Fa-Fi" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 50:7)
  - Gifts & Grants "Fl-Fu" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 51:1)
  - Gifts & Grants "Ga-Gi" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 51:2)
  - Gifts & Grants "Gl-Gu" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 51:3)
  - Gifts & Grants "Ha-He" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 51:4)
  - Gifts & Grants "Hi-Hu" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 51:5)
  - Gifts & Grants "I" and "J" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 51:6)
  - Gifts & Grants "Ka-Ki" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 51:7)
  - Gifts & Grants "Kl-Ku" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 51:8)
  - Gifts & Grants "L" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 51:9)
  - Gifts & Grants "Ma-Mc" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 52:1)
  - Gifts & Grants "Me-Mi" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 52:2)
  - Gifts & Grants "Mo-Mu" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 52:3)
  - Gifts & Grants "N" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 52:4)
  - Gifts & Grants "O" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 52:5)
  - Gifts & Grants "Pa-Pe" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 52:6)
  - Gifts & Grants "Pf-Pu" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 52:7)
  - Gifts & Grants "Q-Rh" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 52:8)
  - Gifts & Grants "Ri-Rom" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 52:9)
  - Gifts & Grants "Ros-Ry" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 52:10)
  - Gifts & Grants "Sa-Sc" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 53:1)
  - Gifts & Grants "Se-Sl" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 53:2)
  - Gifts & Grants "Sm-Sp" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 53:3)
  - Gifts & Grants "St-Su" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 53:4)
  - Gifts & Grants "Ta-Th" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 53:5)
  - Gifts & Grants "Ti-Tu" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 53:6)
  - Gifts & Grants "U" and "V" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 53:7)
  - Gifts & Grants "Wal-Wat" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 53:8)
  - Gifts & Grants "We-Wh" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 53:9)
  - Gifts & Grants "Wi" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 53:10)
  - Gifts & Grants "Wo-Wy" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 54:1)
  - Gifts & Grants "Y" and "Z" (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 54:2)
  - Medical Center - CEO Search (pulled from Seldom Used Files) 2001 Jun.-Oct. (Box-folder 54:3)
  - Medical Center - CEO Search (pulled from Seldom Used Files) 2001 Apr.-May (Box-folder 54:4)
  - Medical Center - Dean of Medicine/Vice President Search (pulled from Seldom Used Files) 2002 Mar.-Apr. (Box-folder 54:5)
  - Medical Center - Dean of Medicine/Vice President Search (pulled from Seldom Used Files) 2001 Feb.-Oct. (Box-folder 54:6)
  - Promotions & Tenure - General (pulled from General Files 2002 (Box-folder 54:7)
  - Student Affairs (pulled from General Files) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 54:8)
  - Virginia Status of University Students Committee File (pulled from Committee Files) 2001-2003 (Box-folder 54:9)